https://msmary.edu/privacy-policy.html

Outdoor Adventures
Student Government Association (SGA)
Student Government Association (SGA)
Student Government Association (SGA)
Experiential Leadership Programs
Activities Management Program (AMP)
Scroll For More
Quicklinks:
Home
Thank you for visiting the Mount St. Mary's University website. Your privacy is very important to us. Simply stated, our policy is to collect no personal information about you when you visit msmary.edu, unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us. When you visit msmary.edu, the web server automatically recognizes only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed the site. This information does not result in the identification of your personal email address or other personal information.
In addition, information is only gathered regarding the volume and timing of access to the site by collecting information on the date, time and pages you visited while at the site. This is done so that the content of the site can be improved. This information is not shared with other organizations. Again, only aggregate information is collected, and your personal information is not identified.If you choose to share personal information, such as by subscribing to an e-newsletter, sending a message, or filling out an electronic form with personal information, the information will only be used for the purposes you authorized. Some of this information may be saved for a designated period of time in order to comply with the state of Maryland's archiving policies. However, information will not be disclosed to third parties or other government agencies, unless required by state or federal law.
If you have other questions about msmary.edu privacy policies, or have suggestions on how these policies can be improved, please feel free to email us at webmaster@msmary.edu or contact us by telephone at 301-447-5366.
Visit
Request Info
Apply
Give
